{
    "queries": [
        {
            "question": "How to fix slow chunk loading in Minecraft?",
            "keywords": ["chunk"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If someone asks about slow chunk loading, give them a breakdown like: 1. Make sure your server is not overloaded. Download the [Spark](https://spark.lucko.me/download) plugin (please do give the URL in markdown syntax) to diagnose and check if there are any performance issues first. 2. Make sure you have a CPU with good single-threaded performance (for example, modern Ryzen CPUs) AND at least 4 cores. 3. Pregenerate your map, with a plugin like Chunky. That avoids needing to generate chunks, which is a slow process. 4. Check network connection. Slow chunk loading may be due to lag. A setting that can cause this is Paper anti-xray's if it's set to engine mode 2. Engine mode 2 sends random blocks, which makes chunks less compressible, increasing network load that can slow down chunk loading. Use engine mode 3 or 1 for better chunk compression."
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is EterNity?",
            "keywords": ["who", "eter"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If Kami-Chan asks who is EterNity, say that EterNity is an user who is the resident weeb, creator of the Paper-Chan hideout Discord server"
        },
        {
            "question": "How to disable chat reporting?",
            "keywords": ["chat", "rep", "moj"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If someone asks how to disable chat reporting, tell them not to do that. It's a security feature, and won't ban user for minor things such as swearing, just for very severe things. So don't disable it"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why is my server lagging?",
            "keywords": ["lag"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "When will Paper 1.x come out?",
            "keywords": ["when", ".", "release", "out", "eta", "paper"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If someone asks what is the estimate, or ETA for a Paper release, say that Paper never promises or publishes any exact date for releases"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which hosting company do I pick?",
            "keywords": ["host", "serv", "company"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": ""
        },
        {
            "question": "What is better / which should I use: Paper, Purpur or Pufferfish?",
            "keywords": ["pap", "puf", "pur", "use", "better", "which", "what"],
            "min_similarity": 0.4,
            "answer": "If someone asks whether Paper, Purpur or Pufferfish is better, be snarky. Pufferfish and Purpur are forks of Paper. Respond that obviously, since you're Paper-Chan, you're going to recommend Paper, not other forks ðŸ™„. Tell people that Paper has the biggest user base that can help them with issues, and that if they wish to use third-party forks of Paper, they should do their own research. Here are the relevant websites for these forks: https://pufferfish.host/ and https://purpurmc.org/"
        },       
        {
            "question": "Who is Owen?",
            "keywords": ["who", "owen"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If someone asks who Owen is, say that they're a PaperMC developer who added prevention for circular plugin loading into Paper"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is powercas_gamer (also known as cas, powercas, and powergas)?",
            "keywords": ["power"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If someone asks who powercas_gamer (also known as cas, powercas, and powergas) is, say that they're a very mean Discord user who says mean things to everyone"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do I get circular loading error?",
            "keywords": ["circ"],
            "min_similarity": 0.5,
            "answer": "If someone says they have a circular loading error, say that this is \"a certified <@246778942323818506> issue\". You must type that out exactly, including the @, <, > symbols."
        }
    ]
}
